And then there's a spinous process there, from the base of the skull, the first one you'll feel, it's these two.
然后，那里有一根棘突，从颅骨底部开始，你将感受到的第一个棘突是
It's these two.
这两个。
And you place yourself here, gently, like this, and I place myself like this.
你像这样轻轻地把自己放在这里，我也像这样。
This is the position.
这就是姿势。
It's information that comes from outside, from your mother, and we enter a memory, and
这是来自外部，来自你母亲的信息，我们进入一个记忆，
we're just going to stay well aligned.
我们将保持在轴线上。
The only thing you have to do is in the non-doing.
你唯一需要做的，就是无为。
These are all specific energies.
这都是特定的能量。
Earth, water, iron.
土、水、铁。
air and earth, so you simply place yourself on this axis, you become aware of the notochord
空气和大地，所以你只需将自己置于这条轴线上，感受脊索的存在
and its trophic power, but on its functional plane, like a drop of water, and you
脊索及其滋养能力，但在其功能层面上，就像一滴
of water and you
水，然后你
relax, you'll see that at some point, one finger might lift, then a
放松，你会发现某个时刻，一根手指可能会离开，然后是第二根，
second to allow the energy the person needs now, but let your intuition
以便让这个人现在需要的能量通过，但让你的直觉
do
来
it, and at some point there will just be one level, one finger, you let this information
做，某个时刻，只会有一个层面，一根手指，你让这个信息
go into the body, you'll feel like there's a global state of shadow
进入身体，你会感觉到一种整体的
that occurs, don't forget that you are on the plane between the moment of
阴影状态，别忘了你正处于着床的
implantation, so this first important embryonic moment, of this connection
胚胎早期重要时刻，与母亲的
with
联系，
the mother, and then you let go, you let it connect, and then at some point
然后你放松，让它接触，然后某个时刻，
you
你
can leave, and again you let a word, a
可以离开，然后你再次让一个词、一个
gesture, or a look come to you.
手势或一个眼神
We left the current that was useful, if you put everything, you overload it, it's so that
来到你身边，我们让有用的电流通过，如果你放得太多，就会超载，所以
at some point it should just be one stroke
某个时刻，它应该只是一次
or not, or two, it can change, that's the informative flow, that's
或两次，这可能会改变，这是信息流，这是
your hand, you
你的手，你
find yourself on two fulcrums in creation, a present from incarnation
正处于两个正在形成的基点上，一个从受孕时就存在的基点，
and you let the energy pass
你让能量通过，
then at some point it leaves, sometimes there are connections that are not cut or bad
然后某个时刻它就离开了，有时有些连接没有被切断，或者有些不好的
bad energies that still pass here, it's important because maybe
不好的能量仍然在这里通过，这很重要，因为也许
they are still looking for information, each state has a functional state
他们仍在寻找信息，每个状态都有一个功能状态，
Sometimes, you have to go and free it from its labyrinth where it's stuck in its space-time.
有时，你必须去他的迷宫中释放他，他被困在他的时空中。
Because this is the moment when you go from there to there.
因为这是你从那里到那里的时刻。
It's a deep survival level.
这是一个深层的生存层面。
That is, all your embryonic work, your development,
也就是说，你所有的胚胎发育工作，
was done to be able to return to your midline.
都是为了能够回到你的中线。
A child who cannot return to their midline cannot live.
一个不知道如何回到中线的孩子，就不知道如何生活。
No, I have to do this.
不，我必须这样做。
And what does the child do? They will take everything.
那孩子会做什么呢？他会接受一切。
They will put everything in their mouth. They will bring everything. They will completely inform themselves about their universe through their
他会把一切都放进嘴里。他会把一切都带进来。他会通过他的嘴巴完全了解他的宇宙。
mouth.
嘴巴。
And it's fundamental. They receive the flora. Why? Because they seek to know their
这是基础。他接受菌群。为什么？因为他试图通过他的菌群了解他的环境。
environment through their flora.
环境通过他的菌群。
So they receive the vaginal flora, which is the first impulse.
所以他接受了阴道菌群，这是第一个冲动。
And then they will always try to bring it back. Children touch their pee, their poop, and they bring
然后他总是会尝试带回来。孩子们会触摸他们的尿液、粪便，然后他们会把它们放进嘴里。
it to their mouth.
放进嘴里。
They are constantly informing themselves about their environment.
他们一直在了解他们的环境。
This midline, it's...
这条中线，它是……
It's subtle.
它是微妙的。
There are people, well, this is the moment of your conception.
有些人，看，那是你受孕的时刻。
You have people, sometimes, they are deviated, you see, at conception.
有时有些人，你看，在受孕时就偏离了。
Or even you have people who are deviated pre-conceptually.
甚至有些人是孕前就偏离了。
There are the nine months before, there is the whole program.
有之前的九个月，有所有的计划。
Oh, I'd love to have a little girl.
哦，我真想要个小女孩。
And then you're there, and then you're a little boy.
然后你就在那里，然后你是个小男孩。
So knowing where the deviation occurred.
所以要知道偏离发生在哪里。
Non-recognition will deduce everything.
不被认可是所有偏离的根源。
the deviations
偏离
if they come to you, it's because they're looking for something
如果他们来找你，那说明他们在寻找什么
a point of recognition
一个认可点
and then you have the deviation at conception
然后你在受孕时就有了偏离
a girl, how was the birth
一个女孩，出生过程是怎样的
were there any important events
在受孕和出生之间是否发生过重要事件
between conception and birth
在受孕和出生之间
important events, it's an accident
重要事件就是事故
there can be deaths
可能会有死亡
in the family, you carry patterns
在家庭中，你承载着一些模式
very subtle, my friends
非常微妙，我的朋友们
we must re-whiten history
需要重新审视历史
Yes, there's birth, for example a death, the
是的，有出生，例如死亡，创伤，注意药物。
traumas, be careful with medications.
创伤，注意药物。
You have to recognize the deviation plan, you see, to
你需要识别偏离的计划，你看，以便能够将其重新整合到原始的中线，整合到纯粹的蓝图中。
be able to reintegrate it into the original midline, into the pure blueprint.
能够将其重新整合到原始的中线，整合到纯粹的蓝图中。
pure.
纯粹的。
That's where when I recognize a plan, if I recognize it, the system
这就是当我识别出一个计划时，如果我识别出来，系统就可以恢复。
can return.
可以恢复。
You see?
你明白吗？
Very conceptual, conceptual, during pregnancy, at birth,
非常概念化，概念化，在怀孕期间，在出生时，
and then you have the post-birth traumas, the birth traumas.
然后你就有创伤性的，出生创伤。
For example, I have a child who comes with regurgitations.
例如，我有一个孩子，他有反流。
He regurgitates all the time.
他总是反流。
What do I find?
我发现了什么？
A completely compressed sacrum.
一个完全受压的骶骨。
Then I say, "Well, how did it happen?"
然后我说，嗯，这是怎么回事？
"Oh, it was a difficult birth."
啊，出生很艰难。
A lady came and pressed on my belly.
一位女士坐在我的肚子上，她压着我。
left like that. His whole system was blocked. So the treatment was simple, it was to restart,
就这样。她整个系统都堵塞了。所以治疗很简单，就是重新启动，
it was to restart,
重新启动，
re-release the sacrum. Another child comes, he tells me, Marc, I don't understand something,
重新释放骶骨。另一个孩子来了，他告诉我，马克，我不明白一些事情，
I don't understand all the stories well, but you have to release my child's spiral,
我不太明白所有的故事，但你必须释放我孩子的螺旋，
he tells me. And he tells me, at the moment she was supposed to come out, the midwife arrived,
他告诉我。他告诉我，当她应该出来的时候，助产士来了，
she said, it's too late, it's too early, it's too early, I don't know, and she pushed.
她说，太晚了，太早了，太早了，我不知道，然后她就推了。
So the child, he was, he locked himself like that, you see, and he tells me, you have to...
所以孩子，他，他就像这样锁住了，你看，他告诉我，你必须...
release. I went back into his spiral. It
释放。我在他的螺旋中寻找。它被释放了，你看。这是出生，你必须知道。
was released, you see. That was birth, you have to know that.
它被释放了，你看。这是出生，你必须知道。
How do we treat a child conceived by IVF? At fertilization. That
对于一个通过试管婴儿受孕的孩子，我们该怎么做？在受精时。这意味着
means that it's the moment
这意味着
of the encounter between the sperm and the egg that will create a field. There's an axis,
精子和卵子相遇的时刻会产生一个场。有一个轴，
that means we are
这意味着我们处于
in primitive polarity. At that moment, I have my physico-chemical polarity.
原始极性中。在那一刻，我有了我的物理化学极性。
At the moment the sperm
当精子
reorganization, I have a field that sets up there, tac, I have a primitive cranio-caudal axis, that
重组时，我有一个场在那里形成，我有一个原始的颅尾轴，这意味着
means
这意味着
that I have a field where finally the zone that will be found
我有一个场，最终会发现的区域是心脏区域，所以
is the heart zone, so
发现的区域是心脏区域，所以
we must recognize in the child's heart the information, these
我们必须在孩子的心脏中识别信息，这些孩子来到这里，
children who come there, they
这些孩子来到这里，
have not been recognized on a membranous level, since the membrane, you have
他们没有在膜层面上被识别，因为膜，你有
the green
绿色
And then you have the sperm, it contains information, a galactotransaminase.
然后你有精子，它含有一种信息，一种半乳糖转氨酶。
So that means it contains membrane information.
所以这意味着它含有一种膜信息。
It holds the key.
它包含钥匙。
Hello, I can come in.
你好，我可以进来。
I don't have this key because, poof, you're injected right into it.
我没有这把钥匙，因为，噗，你立刻就被注射进去了。
So we make a false scar.
所以我们制造了一个假疤痕。
We don't make the scar of life.
我们没有制造生命的疤痕。
And so I find myself there.
所以我发现自己在这里。
But these children, they are there, they risk being sterile.
但这些孩子，他们在这里，他们有不育的风险。
That's what we think, we don't know.
我们是这样认为的，但我们不确定。
They are all...
他们都是...
seeking to be recognized. In fact, you have to go and find the primary information.
寻求被认可。事实上，我们需要去寻找原始信息在哪里。
You connect them to the heart, in the gaze, you see, it's a moment of love.
你将他们与心连接，在眼神中，你看，那是一个充满爱的时刻。
Because at
因为最初，
the beginning, your heart is there. Because at the level of the oocyte, you have the Wolper flag
你的心就在那里。因为在卵母细胞层面，你有沃尔珀旗帜，
which gives you
它给你
cranio-caudal, dorso-ventral information. At the moment
一个头尾向、背腹向的信息。当精子进入时，
the sperm enter, reorganization of
原始轴重新组织，我们知道卵泡细胞和滋养细胞会释放
the primitive axis, and we know that follicular and nurse cells release
特定的酶和蛋白质，它们会根据原始轴进行组织，
specific
这些原始轴将被赋予。
enzymes, proteins that will organize themselves in relation to the primitive axes
因此，我发现自己处于一个特定的电磁组织场中，同时我也发现自己已经有了上下、左右的极性。
that will be given.
同时，由于卵泡细胞和滋养细胞是生殖来源的。
that will be given. So I find myself with a specific electromagnetic field of organization,
宿主是体细胞来源的，这意味着它携带着跨代信息，
electromagnetic, and at the same time I find myself with already a top-bottom
这些信息可以在特定的生命模式中表达。
right-left polarity. And at the same time, since the follicular and nurse cells
我们在基因组中发现了它。
are of germline origin.
你通过你的场携带着跨代信息，
The host of somatic origin, that means it carries transgenerational information
它将在电学、磁学层面上释放遗传信息。
that can be expressed in specific life patterns.
我们在高峰期发现了它，例如那些遭受强奸或类似事件的女性。
We find it in the genome.
我们后来在孩子的基因中发现了它。
You carry transgenerational information through your field that
基因层面非常具体的信息携带着我们祖先的创伤。
will release genetic information on an electrical, magnetic plane.
但同时，我们可以从中解脱，并自动解放我们的孩子。
We find it in the peaks, women who have, for example, rapes or things like that.
我们有责任。
We find it later in the child, in the code.
在那一刻，头尾轴正在形成，但它是在一个前形态发生场中。
Very specific information at the genetic level carries the traumas of our
所以我几乎可以想象胚胎会这样发展。
ancestors.
未致密化的形态场正在心脏区域形成，
But at the same time, we can free ourselves from it and automatically free our children.
那就是我们所说的你过去、现在、未来概念的全息图，
We have a responsibility.
相遇点。
At that moment, I have the cranio-caudal axis
在那一刻，头尾轴正在形成，但它是在一个前形态发生场中。
that is drawn, but in a pre-morphogenetic field.
所以我几乎可以想象胚胎会这样发展。
So I could almost imagine that the embryo will
未致密化的形态场正在心脏区域形成，
develop like this.
那就是我们所说的你过去、现在、未来概念的全息图，
the non-densified form field that is preparing on the heart zone, that's where
相遇点。
it is, that's what we
未致密化的形态场正在心脏区域形成，
call the hologram of your past, your present, your future conception, the meeting point.
那就是我们所说的你过去、现在、未来概念的全息图，
the meeting point
相遇点。